http://www.nearseanaturals.com/pages/privacy-policy

Sign In
Bag (0)
Sales & Promotions
New Arrivals!
Privacy Policy
What Information Does Organic Cotton Plus Collect?
When making a purchase through our Site, we collect your name, billing address, phone number, e-mail address, and credit card information, in order to process your order. Therefore when you visit our Site to place subsequent orders we can save you time by providing your previous account information for you. If you opt-in to our newsletter, you'll be notified by email of news and our special product offers.
We use cookies, which is a feature of your browser used to assign identification to your computer. The unique user ID contained within your cookie automatically identifies your computer - but not you - to our servers every time you visit our site. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to find out the identity of any user, but may be correlated with identity information in our log files. You can decline cookies through your browser preference options, but you may not be able to use some of our services properly as a result, such as the option to save your user name and password.
We also collect the IP address of visitors to our Site, and collect aggregate information about the use of our Site.
How Does Organic Cotton Plus Use The Data It Collects?
We use the Data collected from you primarily to process and fulfill your orders, to notify you of the status of your orders, to send our e-mail newsletter, or to send you targeted marketing information, special product offers, or other information that we believe might interest you. In every such e-mail, we will have instructions on how to unsubscribe and avoid receiving any future e-mails from us.
We also may combine information you have provided to us in communications offline - such as information related to your catalog subscription and orders - with the Data you have given us online, to provide a more customized experience for you when you visit our Site.
Communications from Organic Cotton Plus to you
We may contact you by e-mail to respond to customer service questions you have submitted, or to address a problem affecting your use of the Site, or to send you a confirmation message upon completion of the account registration process.
With Whom Does Organic Cotton Plus Share Information?
Organic Cotton Plus does not share any of your personal information with 3rd parties.
How Is Your Information Protected?
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All orders are transmitted over secure Internet connections using SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption technology. All of your personal information including your credit card information and sign-in password are stored in encrypted format at all times. This Website, and more importantly all user information, is further protected by a firewall based security system.
Correcting And Updating Your Information
Users of our Site are able to modify their account information, such as shipping and billing addresses, each time they place an order with us.
Links To Other Sites
Organic Cotton Plus contains links to other sites not affiliated with Organic Cotton Plus. These sites have their own policies and practices with respect to online privacy, and Organic Cotton Plus cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of these unaffiliated web sites.
Contact Information
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or about Organic Cotton Plus' information collection practices, please contact us at customerservice@organiccottonplus.com
Questions?
Start Here
Sign up for sales + news!
Why Shop With Us?
Same day shipping for most orders
Free Shipping Over $50 For US Orders
Trusted for 21 Years
Quality Guarantee
Happy Customers!
Questions? Call us toll-free at: 1-855-SEW-PURE
© 2020 Organic Cotton Plus   |
Privacy Policy
